<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic_blr_kwd_ddc">
    <title>A Tale As Old As Time</title>
    <shortdesc>Welcome! Come along with me as I tell a tale as old as time. It is the story of
        Belle, a hidden gem in a small village, and how crossing paths with a lonesome beast changed
        her life in a way she never would have imagined.</shortdesc>
    <body>
        <section id="forchildren" audience="children">
            <title>Introduction</title>
            <p>In a land far, far away lived a warm and kindhearted girl named Belle. She lived with
                her dad in the quaint village of Villeneuve, where everyone knew each other. She
                would teach children how to read, as well as help other members of the community
                with many different things. There was also Gaston, who always had his eyes on her.
                He "loved" her and wanted to marry her for her looks. Little did she know what her
                future would hold...</p>
        </section>
        <image href="indexpic.jpg" id="image_qkf_tbr_fdc" audience="children"
            alt="Belle smiles at her father as she helps him fix something in his shop." scale="30"/>
        <section id="foradults" audience="adults">
            <title>Introduction</title>
            <p>In a land far, far away lived a kind and pure-hearted girl named Belle. She lived
                with her dad, Maurice, in the quaint village of Villeneuve, where everyone knew each
                other. She would teach children how to read, as well as help other members of the
                community with various tasks. There was also Gaston, who always pursued her and
                flirted with her. He loved her the moment he set his eyes on her--almost as much as
                he loved himself. Little did she knowwhat her future would hold and what road she
                would go down that would eventually lead her to finding true love.</p>
        </section>
        <fig id="fig_y3m_b4d_ddc" audience="adults">
            <image href="indexpic.jpg" id="indexpic"
                alt="Belle smiles at her father as she helps him fix something in his shop."
                scale="30"/>
        </fig>
    </body>
</topic>
